Guide to the Rice University Campus Photographer Files, 1970-2004 UA 188
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Addenda, transferred in 2011, 115370
  - Subseries C: Students, faculty, staff, departments, groups, visitors, and speakers, 115521
    - Subseries F: Sallyport and other publications, 117512
      - Sallyport - Antarctica, 118795 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Sallyport, Spring 2000; 118796 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Sallyport, Winter 2000; 118797 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Sallyport, Spring 2001; 118798 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Sallyport, Summer 2001; 118799 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Sallyport, Fall 2001; 118800 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Sallyport, Spring 2002; 118801 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Sallyport, Summer 2002; 118802 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Sallyport, Fall 2002; 118803 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Sallyport, Winter 2002; 118804 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Sallyport, Summer 2003; 118805 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Sallyport, Fall 2003; 118806 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Sallyport, Winter 2003; 118807 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Sallyport, Spring 2004; 118808 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Viewbook, 2001; 118809 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Viewbook, 2002-2003; 118810 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Viewbook, 2003-2004; 118811 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Board Face Book, 1999; 118812 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Board Face Book, 2001; 118813 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - News From Fondren, Spring 2000; 118814 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - News From Fondren, 2001; 118815 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - News From Fondren, Spring 2002; 118816 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - News From Fondren, Spring 2003; 118817 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Golden Anniversary Scholarship Newsletter images, 118818 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Jones Journal, 2000; 118819 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Jones Journal #8, 2003; 118820 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Subseries D: Athletics/Sports, 116765
    - Athletics Banquet, October 1998; 116766 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Athletics trainers, 116767 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Cox Fitness Center, 116768 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Cheerleaders, 116769 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Coaches, 116770 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Fans, 116771 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Owl Club, 116772 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Rally Club, 116773 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Sammy - mascot, 117978 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Intramurals, 116774 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Baseball, 1999; 116777 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Baseball, 2000; 116778 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Baseball - Championship Coke bottles, 116775 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Baseball - College World Series games 1-3, 116776 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Basketball - men's, 116779 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Basketball - men's, 116781 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Basketball - women's, 116780 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Basketball camps, 116783 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Crew, 116782 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Fencing, 116784 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Football - Texas Children's Hospital, 116786 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Football, 116785 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Football, 116787 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Football - last SWC game, 116789 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Football - Rice vs. UT, 1994; 116790 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Football, 1996; 116791 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Football - Rice vs. Air Force, 1997; 116792 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Football, 1998; 116793 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Football, 1999; 116794 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Football, 2000; 116795 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Golf, 116796 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Lacrosse - men's, 116797 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Lacrosse - women's, 116798 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Rugby, 116799 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Soccer, 116800 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Soccer camp, July 2000; 116802 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Swimming - men's, 116803 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Swimming - women's, 116804 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Tennis, 116805 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Track and Field, 116806 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Volleyball, 116808 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Subseries E: Rice-related material and other media, 116578
    - Rice University campus banners, 117633 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Rice University emblems, 116574 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Rice University seal, 116575 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Rice University fund, 116576 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Rice mascot - live owls, 118635 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Rice merchandise, 118067 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Rice bus images, 118634 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Plants, 118636 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Harper Leiper Order Book, 118762 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - A Place in Time: Photgraphic Reflections, by John Boles, March 2003; 116689 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - "The Rice Institute" by Bill Condon - Museum of Fine Arts Houston, 117993 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Rice Identity Program, 118763 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Rice Information Systems, 118764 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Rice: The Next Century Campaign, 118765 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Rice: The Next Century Campaign, 118766 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Campus Tours, 118767 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Welcome Center kiosk, 118768 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Brochure - Athletic Scholarship, 118769 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Brochures and invitations - Baker, 118770 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Brochure - Endowed Scholarship, 118771 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Brochure - Executive Education Corp. Programs, 118772 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Brochure - F and E Hoots, 118773 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Brochure - Humanities Fundraising (watercolor), 118774 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Brochure and inserts - Humanities/Visual Arts, 118775 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Brochure - IBB Fundraising, 118776 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Brochure - Minter Endowment Fund, 118777 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Brochure - NBIE, 118778 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Brochure - Pacesetter, 118779 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Brochure - PREP Program, 118780 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Brochures - Rice, 118781 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Brochure - Shepherd School Preparatory images, 118783 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Book and magazine covers, 118784 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Rice-Houston Engagement, 118782 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Admissions - Parents' Guide, 2000; 118785 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Campaign Case Statement, 118790 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Alumni - Football nametags, 118786 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Rice Fact Sheet, November 2003; 118787 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Student biographies, 118788 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Suzanne Craig Represents - illustration samples, 118789 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Keck Hall dedication package, 118791 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Koplowitz poster and postcards, 118792 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Telefund meeting postcard images, 118793 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Gillis inauguration photo packets, 118794 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Sallyport - Antarctica, 118959 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Sallyport, Spring 2000; 118960 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Sallyport, Winter 2000; 118962 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Sallyport, Spring 2001; 118961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Sallyport, Summer 2001; 118963 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Sallyport, Fall 2001; 118964 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Sallyport, Spring 2002; 118965 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Sallyport, Summer 2002; 118966 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Sallyport, Fall 2002; 118967 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Sallyport, Winter 2002; 118968 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Sallyport, Summer 2003; 118943 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Sallyport, Fall 2003; 118944 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Sallyport, Winter 2003; 118945 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Sallyport, Spring 2004; 118946 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Viewbook, 2001; 118947 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Viewbook, 2002-2003; 118948 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Viewbook, 2003-2004; 118949 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Board Face Book, 1999; 118950 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Board Face Book, 2001; 118951 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - News From Fondren, Spring 2000; 118952 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - News From Fondren, 2001; 118953 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - News From Fondren, Spring 2002; 118954 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - News From Fondren, Spring 2003; 118955 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Golden Annniversary Scholarship Newsletter No. 2, 118956 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Jones Journal, 118957 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Jones Journal Issue 8, 118958 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - DVD - sports images, 119060 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - DVD - photographs and file, 2001-2005; 119061 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - CD - Chinatown to Rice U, Bob Handelman, 119062 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - CD - Kindra Welch, Gregory Benson Photography (1 of 2), 119063 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - CD - Kindra Welch, Gregory Benson Photography (2 of 2), 119064 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - CD - Martel College, Michael Graves and Associates, 119066 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Subseries F: Construction
    - Color slides of campus construction, 1996-2000 (Box 49)